bizhwy.com 2006-06-19

# Business Directory Listings

**THE SUMMARY**  
BizHwy.com will not ask you for information that does not have a purpose and we will not require information to be disclosed that is not absolutely necessary. BizHwy.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to others. 

**THE DETAILS**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice shall apply to all information BizHwy.com collects or is submitted by the user on the BizHwy.com website. To make this notice easy to find; we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Use of Customer Information**  
BizHwy.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, rent, or disclose this information to third parties. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**  
This site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that BizHwy.com is in no way responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our customers to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the BizHwy.com website.
